Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trials, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
I'm gonna use all of my magic, then everything will be destroyed!
You, the rest of these humans, and even me! I want all of you revolting humans to disappear for good!
What's going on with this key?
Locke had been reincarnated as a vengeful elf, bent on devastating the human race.
That's why I swear I'll make you pay!
I don't know what you're talking about, but if humans are to blame for what happened, I'm sorry! I really mean it!
But look, he's precious to us! We're friends! And we wouldn't ever want to lose him! So please, don't take him away!
Take him away!
That's right!
Let go of him before it's too late!
I'm sure the people you cared about wouldn't want you to make someone else go through that same pain you did back then!
Get out!
As Oster, Vanessa, and Magna struggled to bring luck back, their bonds of friendship were felt once again.
Once again.
Um...
Guys...
Tell me, can...
Can I still be...
In the black balls?
What are you talking about, kid?
Of course you can.
How do you remember him from there?
Such tears...
I know...
Enter...
He's not a fan of!
Let's relax, don't listen to it
In my love, don't forget to close the door
It's the beginning of the door
Do what, do, do what?
Let's not do it
Let's ...
We're getting ...
桐 桐 じた世界で 負けられる戦い
président ビクりする blue like a bear
BO It Soo Let's not love, love, love
負けるわけないじゃん
炊 胃炎にもならこそそく结績参考以上
憑来頑いかさせていく寸心を無駄にあたに
I'm so ...
ちょとちゃん
Tap with a solution to the wind
I met some feeling
As if people get câmb interpret me
Or they stay missing
Stop Zeitge, right?
No one can strike me
We won't matter you
Then we won't make it
It's dreaming
To create a 여기서
Seriously, we will cease
All of us will be
Plus, we are ready
Let's
I'm doing it.
Yeah!
Let's go!
Hasta magna Vanessa and the recently rescued Luck,
reunited with Gordon Gray Charmy and their newly
discovered squadmate Henry.
Then, the group boarded the Raging Black Bull
and raced toward the capital.
Basta!
There are three elves in that town ahead!
How pathetic.
This town was so glorious.
Now it's just a pile of debris.
They'll all be dead soon.
Mommy! Daddy!
It's no use. They're too strong.
Why, Lord Zergs? I don't understand this.
Why would the saint of pure eyes hurt the ones he's meant to help?
If magic knights are turning on us,
there's no hope left for the Clover Kingdom.
Soul, I failed. I couldn't protect the town.
But still, I refuse to give up until the very end.
I'm going to purify everything now,
including you filthy humans.
Ice magic!
Hmm?
What's wrong?
Something's approaching.
What is that?
An enemy?
They can try whatever weak defenses they want,
but they will never succeed against us.
Stone magic!
Ground wall!
Recombenation magic!
Raging Blackppoel combat style!
Hat!
Recombenation magic!
Raging Blackpoel combat style!
Er, is that a bow?
Yes.
Ah, why would it have to?
Uh...
Yeah!
Rescue!
I gotcha!
Transformation magic!
Magic conversion!
Ice to water!
Oh, it's bad!
I was so scared!
Thanks for your help, Miss!
Don't mention it!
And please, can you stop looking at me?
That robe...
She must be a black bull.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
Don't get a big head, humans.
I'm about to destroy that hunk of garbage!
Water magic! Searching waves!
Stone magic!
Rising ground!
It's not working.
It's diverting our spells somehow.
I wish you two would stop wasting time.
Ice magic!
Ice slicer!
What? What happened?
As long as I've still got some magic left, the Black Bulls will not be harmed.
Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike! Mike!
Okay! Here we go!
Flame Magic Gargantuan Exploding Fireball!
How about some lightning magic? Thunderbolt Destruction!
Poison Magic. Forbidden Fruits.
We're combining all three of our offensive abilities!
To crush you!
Alright! It looks like the shut-in's really got some skills, huh?
Good job, Henry!
I'm proud. So proud that I've already made a doll for him.
That's because I know my friends so well. We're squad mates, so that's important!
What else does it do?
Finally, I get to fight with the others! I'm so glad!
Do it, Henry!
I've had quite enough of your foolishness.
You might manage to dodge this.
But the town won't survive!
Farewell, humans! Combo Magic!
Oscar Cannon!
Fire!
You don't ever mess with the Black Bulls! We're invincible!
I felt it for as long as I can remember. Someone else was lying dormant within me. I got the sense that they were badly wounded.
Insatiably angry. And overwhelmingly sad all at once. And so, I began to feel the responsibility to protect that weak being. Because I knew that my body wasn't just mine.
Because I understood they were always with me. That's why I was able to make it through such a lonely and painful childhood.
About the time I turned nine years old, I started having a recurring dream. A dream about much happier days. It turned out, those were your memories.
But it ended in disloyalty, despair, and bitter hatred.
I believe that it was up to me to make sure you were safe. And then, when I was thirteen, I met Julius.
William, I want you to join the Magic Knights!
He was strange, but he was the first person to acknowledge me.
Oh, right. I suppose you won't be receiving your grimoire until you turn fifteen. So I'll just keep dropping by from time to time until that happens.
He was kind. I looked up to him.
I have no doubt that you'll be a spectacular magic knight.
Then, when I was sixteen, you awakened.
What is this place? What happened to me? I thought... I was dead.
Around that time, I was a newcomer affiliated with the Grey Deer, the Magic Knight Squad led by Julius.
When you also received your grimoire, it confirmed the suspicion I'd always held that you and I were two separate souls inhabiting the same body.
Eventually, we became able to communicate our thoughts telepathically, and we could even swap souls with each other.
I soon learned that you had a mission you were set on completing at any cost.
And for that, I would have to betray the other person closest to me, as well as the kingdom I called home.
I was forced to choose between you, the one with whom I'd shared everything as though we were twins, and the admirable leader of the Magic Knights, the man who taught me how to live my life.
It was an impossibly difficult decision to make, but the longer I debated, the more of my comrades were hurt.
In the end, I failed to commit either way, and I let both of you choose the outcome.
I'm a monster. You got what you wanted. I'm sorry, Julius. Patry, you won.
And now, since you've finally achieved your ambition, this is where we part ways.
So goodbye, Patry. And maybe...
I must have expended too much power. Was I asleep? How long?
My own reincarnation has been completed at last.
Which means William has fallen into an endless slumber.
Thank you, to the only human I could call my friend.
William.
Goodbye.
At this point, there is no longer any human I cannot kill.
Ligt and Raya should be making their way into the royal capital by now.
I'd better make haste.
Clover Castle.
The place where we will exact our revenge.
The royals are concentrated there.
And they're the humans we despise most.
In the moment he was revived, the fear for his life combined with immense hatred caused Rady's magic to grow to a point that he could do more than control the dead.
What resulted was the perfection of true wraith magic.
An evolved technique that was just barely capable of taking souls that were about to be sacrificed and reincarnating them into their bodies.
How could you dare deceive me and convince me to do your bidding only to slaughter and cast me aside?
Curse you!
I'll make you pay for this if it's the last thing I do!
You two.
Rise and shine.
Vatos!
Sally!
What a lucky break!
I almost couldn't bring you guys back!
Now let's kill him!
Together!
We did it!
All three of them are back to normal!
Alright!
Spatial magic.
You three.
What do you want?
Ah, the black balls again.
I'm here for my revenge.
And you're gonna help me get it!
Oh no, it's them!
They're the people who tore down our hideout.
Oh, is that so?
Then you must be the ones responsible for the death of my poor innocent vegetables!
Lasting perfectly good food is a serious crime around here!
Be quiet!
You get it on my nerves too!
But my first priority is killing off that bastard Litt!
Huh?
He tricked me!
He tricked all of us!
Just so that he could use us to serve his own purposes!
And then he threw us away like trash as soon as he didn't need us anymore!
He should pay for what he's done.
And I won't rest until we even the score!
Litt's headed for the royal capital.
I'm assuming he's already there.
If we use Sally's dark magic items to enhance Valto's spatial magic, we'll be able to transport this moving base of yours pretty quickly!
We can be there before you know it!
You're on your way to the royal capital too, aren't you?
It sounds like we all have the same objective here so we might as well work together!
Not a bad deal, right?
Hope you're ready, Litt!
You're as good as dead now!
Judging by the mana, it feels like all of the elves are trying to gather in the capital too!
Wait a minute.
It's kinda sketchy to me that this guy suddenly showed up asking us for help.
Ha!
Well, looks like we got our s-
No way!
What the hell is wrong with you?
You think we're after the same thing?
You better think again!
All we're trying to do is protect everyone!
We're not doing it to get revenge!
And what's worse...
You're the guy who attacked all those innocent people in the capital!
Did you think we forgot about that?
Cause we did it!
And you have the nerve to ask us for help?
You're barking up the wrong tree, pal!
You don't deserve revenge, you dummy!
You need to make up for what you did!
And you can start off by helping us save the Clover Kingdom!
Ah!
Are you kidding me? There's no way I'm gonna do that!
Does it look like I'm playing around to you?
No arguments!
We're in a hurry here, so help us get to the capital right now!
Who died to put you in charge, Pipsqueak?
This isn't a fair deal at all! I won't do it!
You got no choice!
I won't let you go until you agree!
Damn! How are you so strong?
That's our Osta!
Look at him squirm!
That's it! Show him what's what, Osta!
Hang on. We've already got a ride, so do we actually need that guy?
Not sure.
That's a good point, Luck. I guess I'll just have to make a deal with the other two.
Wait! No!
So, uh, what do you guys think of that?
Well, I...
I just want to see Master Lick, so that I can determine the truth.
Therefore, I will accompany you.
After all, if everything Master Lick said was a lie, then I really am a sinner.
Which means I need to seek atonement.
Thanks for nothing, Valtos!
What about you, Sally? You want to get revenge too, don't you?
I don't have my glasses, so I can't see too well.
But you can hear, can't you?
Let me think here. The reason I joined Master Lick was because he let me do whatever experiments I wanted.
And Magic Knights always get in my way.
Then again, I guess I am happy to be alive so I can continue my research.
Oh, and I saw lots of interesting stuff while I was dying, so I might be close to a breakthrough!
I was the one who brought you back to life in case you didn't realize!
Oh, okay. Thanks, Radies!
Hey! You wanted to experiment on me, right?
If you help us stop the Eye of the Midnight Sun and protect the Clover Kingdom, then I'll be your number one test subject!
Huh? Wow, you mean it? That's awesome!
You can't do anything that's going to hurt me really bad.
Don't awe at me!
Come on, as long as you don't hurt anybody, you'll be free to do as much science as your little heart desires!
In fact, if you're doing research that makes the world better, we'll be there to support you a hundred percent!
That would make you happy too, wouldn't it?
I'm kind of confused, but if I get to keep researching, then that's what I want to do.
Sounds good!
And you don't need anesthesia when I cut you off?
Yes, I do! Did you not hear anything I just told you? If not for me, you'd still be dead as a doornail right now!
Mulling it over?
Indeed.
Poor thing. You must be starving. Have some food.
Tastes so good! It's restoring my magic!
What?! That's so cool! I'm hungry too! Let me have some, please!
No one can fight on an empty tummy! Now start eating!
It's delicious! Makes me feel like I could dissect things all day!
Except about that anesthesia!
But this isn't fair! There's plenty more! Is this food making you guys want to defend the Clover Kingdom with us?!
Go on, chill down! After a nap like that, you must have a big appetite!
Eat!
You always feel better than eating with friends is eating food that replenishes your magic power with friends!
I've got the energy to take on anyone in the world!
Why are you still debating? This food is so tasty! You should be convinced!
Best thing ever! You gotta try it, dude!
Oh yeah, wow! I've never been this motivated!
Good! It's amazing!
What a time to be alive! Especially if you were just dead!
That's true! Only the living can enjoy a big bowl of yummy food! You know?
Find you in! We'll go with your squad to the Royal Capital!
But don't think that means you're gonna tell me what to do, you understand?!
I do what I want!
Except you literally just did what I asked you to do!
Get over it already, man! You're siding with the good guys from now on, whether you like it or not!
Shut up!
Pilot as high as you like! There's plenty more food where that came from!
Hurry! The faster you eat, the sooner we can head out!
Once your magic comes back, we'll be off to the capital!
Yeah!
I hate this!
Let's go!
No one stays walking
The next road was no Bulso
Something forgot about it
I couldn't process the道
I've had to
Thank you.
Does it hurt?
How much?
I think I might try this on some of my experiments.
No anesthesia.
Shut up, Sally!
I'm not doing!
Time for the Clover Olaf!
Since you're already in pain, I can dissect you now, can't I?
You don't mind.
Oh, yes, I do mind!
And Bob's off, you idiot!
It's a three count, not a 30 count!
Black Clover, page 107, the battle for Clover Castle.
My name is Henry.